没有一个人在
No one is around.
又是这样
Again.
是我多心了 还是大家最近都在躲着我们
Is it just me or people have been avoiding us lately?
我懂的 养双胞胎太艰辛了
I get it, twins are a ton of work.
但海莉和迪兰非常经常叫我们帮忙
But Haley and Dylan ask us to help out a lot.
或许我们只是因为缺觉而变得神志恍惚了
Maybe we're both just loopy from sleep deprivation.
我都不记得我泡了这杯茶
I don't even remember making this cup of tea.
没事 我跟他们一起去慢跑吧
It's fine, I'll just jog with them.
你跑步别把自己逼得太狠
Don't push yourself too hard on that run.
拜托 你知道你在跟谁说话吗
Please. You know who you're talking to?
为什么大家总是问我这个问题
Why does everyone always ask me that?
好险啊
That was close.
-他们走了吗 -是的
- Are they gone? - Yes.
好了 谁想来当我的魔术助手
Okay, who'd like to help me with a magic trick?
艾丽克斯 好极了
Alex. Great.
你拿着这只鸽子
Now, uh, take this dove --
别激怒它
Try not to rile her up.
它将在我的裤子里待上近一个小时呢
She's about to spend the better part of an hour in my pants.
到目前为止 我们遇到的租客普遍都比较糟心
Until now, we haven't had the best of luck with renters.
你在申请表上说 你是个喜欢猫的人...
So, when you said you were a cat person on your application...
那 只是我手表的反光而已
Oh, oh, that's -- that's just my watch.
但后来布拉德和保罗搬来了 那简直就像
But then Brad and Paul moved in, and it was like
自动送上门的完美夫夫朋友
the perfect friend couple showed up at our front door.
在那个"猫女"之后 你还不想再出租了
And you wanted to stop renting completely after the cat lady.
我无法忍受她每次洗澡时发出的嚎叫
I just -- I couldn't listen to her scream every time she took a bath.
我简直不敢相信我们竟然有这么多共同点
I can't believe how much we have in common.
女儿同龄 你们也都玩橄榄球
Daughters the same age, you both played football.
我的一个前队友现在是洛杉矶闪电队的教练
You know, an ex-teammate of mine is a coach for the Chargers.
他可以让我们上球场
He can get us right on the field.
不过你在选择站位时一定要小心了
You just have to watch where you stand,
因为你可能会处于外接手的下面
'cause you could end up under a wide receiver.
好了 别再推销了 我同意了
Okay, stop selling! I'm in!
他们甚至预付了六个月的租金
They even pre-paid for six months.
那意味着他们会一直住到圣诞节
That means they'll be here till Christmas.
我们可以邀请他们一起玩秘密圣诞老人的游戏
We can include them in our Secret Santa!
可以逃过收莉莉礼物也挺不错的
Oh, it would be nice not to get Lily again.
杜克[约翰·韦恩]
The Duke...
变成了尤克[里里]
becomes a uke...
再变成卢克
becomes a Luke.
爸 这太神奇了
Dad, that was amazing!
神奇的是 我竟然认为这种垃圾小把戏
Amazing that I think a hacky parlor trick
有资格出现在南加房宴上
is gonna cut it at SCARB.
你没听错 艾丽克斯 南加房宴
You heard me right, Alex -- SCARB!
南加州地区房地产经纪人盛宴
The Southern California Area Realtors' Banquet
对南加州地区的房地产经纪人来说
is the biggest event of the year
是年度最盛大的活动
for Southern California Area Realtors.
其他一些活动 比如南加协宴
The other events -- SCARL,
南加联宴 南加会宴 南加群宴...
SCARD, SCARP, SCARG, SCARF --
也挺好的 但南加房宴 才是业内的顶级盛会
t-they're fine, but SCARB, it's -- it's the show.
我在去年的南加房宴上表演了
I performed at last year's SCARB,
我表现得挺好的
and -- and I did well.
好过头了
Too well.
谢谢大家
Thank you.
等等 还有人要说谢谢吗
Wait, was there someone else who wanted to say thank you?
没错
Oh, that's right.
蓬蓬也想说声谢谢
Puff wanted to say thank you.
非常感谢 谢谢
Thank you so much. Thank you.
难以置信
Unbelievable!
你在水下憋了9分钟
When you were underwater for nine minutes,
我都想亲自砸缸救人了
I almost broke the glass myself!
你明年一定要接着来表演
You have got to come back next year.
我想我可以
Well, I guess I could, uh...
在你身后 支持你这话
...get behind you on that.
我都不知道我是怎么做到的
I don't know how I did that.
去年一整年
For the last year,
我去加州任何房产经纪人酒吧 就没花钱买过酒
I haven't paid for a drink in any Realtor bar in California.
我从未见识过那种奉承
I've never known that kind of adulation.
如果我今晚演砸了 这一切就都没了
If I blow it tonight, it all goes away.
我就成了又一个走进中介酒吧的流浪汉
I'm just another bum walking into Brokers
要自己掏钱买"长托管冰茶"
paying for my own Long Escrow Iced Tea!
爸 我现在很有希望拿到太空总署的这份工作
Dad, I'm on the short list for this NASA job.
我需要填好这些表
I just need to finish these forms,
但我发誓 你刚刚的表演真的很棒
but I -- I swear to you, it really was great.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我可是个很难取悦的观众
And I am a tough audience.
我是个科学家
I'm a scientist.
我可不会被简单的误导欺骗
It's not like I'm fooled by simple misdirection.
我跟珍妮丝说我21岁了
I told Janice I'm 21.
我很确定 如果让她发现
I'm pretty sure she'd break up with me
我还没到法定年龄 肯定会跟我分手
if she found out I wasn't even legal yet.
然后她问我能不能为今晚的晚餐买瓶红酒
Then she asked if I'd buy wine for dinner tonight.
能把手指移开吗
Mind moving your thumb...
亚历桑德拉
Alexandra?
原来二姐的名字全名是这样啊
That's what that's short for?
你愿意带他们去公园 真是太好了
So sweet of you to take them to the park.
不过记得一定要找阴凉处
Just make sure they're someplace shady.
我会的
Will do.
你靠售卖家族祖传辣酱发家致富
It's amazing how well you've been doing
发展得这么好 真是太棒了
selling Aunt Miranda's hot sauce.
我都懒得跟你提
I don't want to tell you
我试图在这边卖那个辣酱亏了多少钱
how much money I have lost trying to sell it over here.
我倒是不介意知道一下具体亏损数额...
I wouldn't mind having an exact figure --
我简直不敢相信你们已经订婚了
I can't believe that you guys are already engaged!
你们是在哪里认识的
Where did you guys meet?
在我卖画的那条街上
On the street where I sell my artwork.
有一天 她让我给她画像
One day, she let me paint her.
她成了我的灵感女神
She became my muse.
我真是太为你开心了 桑娅
I am so happy for you, Sonia.
你终于找到你值得拥有的真爱了
Finally, you found the love that you deserve.
我很高兴看到你这么支持桑娅...
It's great seeing you being supportive of Sonia for --
她是个白痴
She's an idiot.
那男的明显是个傍大款的
He's obviously a gold digger,
我要向她证明这点
and I'm going to prove it to her.
你怎么知道他是个傍大款的
How do you know he's a gold digger?
他是个穷困潦倒的画家 她是个富婆
He's a starving artist, she has money.
你真觉得像他那么年轻又好看的人
Do you really think that someone young and beautiful like that
会爱上一个年纪大很多的有钱人吗
is gonna fall in love with a rich, older person?
永远没可能的
Never happens.
我听出我这话里的意思了 我们之间没事
I hear what I'm saying, and we're fine.
等谢丽尔·麦克雷进来时
When Sheryl McCray comes in,
用这张卡给她的咖啡买单
pay for her coffee with this.
谢丽尔·麦克雷 强大房地产开发商
Sheryl McCray, Powerhouse real-estate developer.
我多年来一直希望他们把衣柜业务交给我们来做
I've been trying to land her closet business for years,
但无论如何就是约不上她
but it's impossible to get a meeting.
但是 这篇文章写了
This article, though,
她每周六早上十点买拿铁的地点
says where she buys a latte every Saturday at 10:00.
今天 我要给她买杯拿铁
Today, I'm gonna buy that latte, we'll get to talking,
然后我们就开始聊天 不知不觉
and before you know it,
她就会"拿铁"衣柜的订单到我手里
she'll be buying a latte closets.
谢丽尔·麦克雷吗
Sheryl McCray?
马修·康 来自康氏橱柜
Matthew Kang, Kang Cabinets.
能给我两分钟的时间坐下来...
Would you have just two minutes to, uh, sit dow--
你有没有搞错
Are you serious?
我不会和你这种
I'm not gonna do business with someone
居然打断我单独和我孩子
who interrupts me in a coffee shop
以及孩子的保姆在咖啡店
while I'm trying to enjoy a few precious moments
享受美好时光的人做生意
of alone time with my child. And her nanny.
我觉得她尿湿了
I think she's wet.
计划有变吗 土豪
Change of plans, big spender?
真的吗 紧急情况吗
Ohh! Really? An emergency?
我想我能
Well, I guess I could --
放松 他们不需要帮忙带孩子
Relax. They don't need help with the babies.
卢克带着呢
Luke has them.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
赶紧把这破杂志丢一边
Ugh. Let's get rid of this bad reminder, huh?
我认识她
Oh, I know that lady.
什么 怎么认识的
What? How?
在瑜伽房的"妈妈和我"课上认识的
Oh, Mommy and Me class at my yoga place,
她每周都在那
she's there every week.
正好 再过半个小时就要开始了
Oh, in fact, it's starting in half an hour.
我该带着孩子过去上课啦
Think I'm gonna grab the kids and go do my thang.
你知道吗
You know what?
我都没好好和这俩小家伙待过呢
I haven't spent any time with those little ragamuffins.
让我带他们去吧
Why don't you let me take 'em?
-但我有点想 -接受帮助吧
- But I kind of wanted to take-- - Oh, take the help!
别逞英雄啦 超级妈妈
Don't be a hero, super mom, huh?
是我觉得 还是你们也觉得你妈有点怪
Is it me, or is your mom acting weird?
不不
No. No!
不要 你这个
Don't you ev--
听到咒语再出来
Your cue is "Cadabra"!
我们做了甘蓝冰沙 分一些给你们
We made kale smoothies. We wanted to share.
谢谢
Thank you.
不好意思 我们好像打扰你们了
Oh, no! We're intruding.
你们在举办薄饼早午餐会呢
You're throwing a big pancake brunch.
其他人呢
Where is everyone?
这只是我们自己吃的
Uh, this is just for us.
-这是什么 -学校的艺术项目
- What's this? - Art project for school.
我就随便从垃圾里找了个东西
I just grabbed something out of the trash
然后粘了点闪光胶水
and threw glitter glue on it.
就得了70
Got a 70.
她知道总分是100吧
She knows that's out of 100, right?
薇拉正在处于艺术发现阶段
Vera went through a Found Art phase.
这是
This is, um...
这是她用塑料做的
This is the Michelangelo's David
米开朗基罗的大卫像
that she made out of plastic.
再生塑料
Recycled plastic.
我们只有一个星球 我们要保护它
We only get one planet, let's take care of it.
看来有人没听过月球
Guess someone's never heard of the moon.
说起来艺术 你们太幸运了
Oh, hey, speaking of art, you're so lucky
住这里离博物馆那么近
to live right around the corner from the museum.
后印象派展览里谁是你们最喜欢的艺术家
Who was your favorite artist in the postimpressionist show?
非要我说的话
I mean, gun to my head?
我会说
I would say...
高更[再去]吗
Gauguin, perhaps?
去展览吗 当然 想都不用想
To the exhibit? Yes. In a heartbeat.
事实上我想今天过去
Uh, you know, actually, I'm thinking about going today.
你们要一起吗
Would you guys care to join?
我很想去
Oh, I'd love to,
但我答应这位要一起峡谷徒步
but I promised this one we'd go on a canyon hike.
他曾经是内衣模特
Once an underwear model...
为了赚医学院的学费
A couple International Male covers
上过几次《国际男性》的封面而已
to pay for medical school,
他一直提
he'll never let me forget it!
好了 我们该走了
Okay, we should go.
或者你们想一起去徒步吗
Oh! Unless, did you want to join for the hike?
不好意思 我今天下午
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm -- I'm running the Santa Monica stairs
要去爬圣塔莫尼卡台阶 所以
this afternoon, so...
今天是周六
Oh. It's Saturday.
大家伙儿看不到我会着急的
If they don't see me there, they get worried.
谢谢你们的冰沙
And thank you for the yummies.
真的好好喝
They sure are!
一点也不好吃
Oh, no.
我都不知道你喜欢博物馆呢
So, um, I didn't know you were a museum lover.
在咱俩开始约会之前
Oh, well, yeah, before you and I started dating,
我总是去博物馆
I used to go to the museum all the time.
当然 我不是在怪你
I'm not blaming you, of course.
你知道好莱坞名人蜡像博物馆
You know that the Hollywood Wax Museum
不是真正的...
isn't an actual --
你呢 猛男洛奇
Okay, what about you, Rocky?
你拿毛巾上楼都气喘吁吁
You get winded taking towels upstairs.
是因为遇到你之后 不是怪你哦
Well, that's because after we met -- not blaming you --
我有点 我逐渐不爬了
um, I sort of -- I tapered off a little bit.
为了专注于咱俩的感情
To focus on the relationship.
但这样很好啊
But this is good.
我们重回原来的状态
Yeah. Us getting back to our roots.
享受博物馆
You know, enjoy the museum.
-享受你的跑步 -我会的
- Yeah, enjoy your run. - I will.
或许你还没...
You haven't, by chance --
他们还在盒子里
They're still in the box.
-橱柜后面吗 -是的
- Back of the closet? - Uh-huh.
你怎么从来没让我玩过那个东西
How come you never let me play with that thing?
这东西可在三个航空展上获过奖 曼尼
This "thing" medaled in three different Air Expos, Manny.
它可不是玩具
It's not a toy.
看这个
Hey, look at this.
这是桑娅的未婚夫 对吧
That's Sonia's fiance, right?
据说他来自哥伦比亚最富有的家族
It says he's from one of the richest families in Colombia.
我知道那家伙不错的
I knew the guy was all right.
我明白了 有钱就是不错
Oh, I see. Being rich makes you "all right."
我不是这个意思
That's not what I meant.
你妈以为他可能是来傍大款的
Your mom thought he might be a gold digger.
而且不像你 我可是成长于工薪阶级
And by the way, unlike you, I grew up working-class.
得了 这个家里唯一的蓝领[项圈]
Oh, please. The only blue collar in this house
就是你纯种法国斗牛犬脖子上的亮晶晶项圈
is the bedazzled one on your purebred French bulldog.
她最近挺抑郁的
She was going through a depressed period.
家里最不开心的孩子 影响着父母开心的上限
You're only as happy as your least happy child, Manny.
我只是说 我从没见过
I'm just saying, I've never seen you
你对没钱的人感兴趣
show much interest in someone who didn't have money.
胡说
That's ridiculous.
老兄 过来歇歇吧
Hey, buddy! Come on, take a load off.
-一起喝一杯 -谢谢你先生
- Have a drink with us. - Oh, thank you, sir.
我知道辛苦工作一天是什么感觉
I know what it's like to put in a hard day's work.
杰·普里契特 顺便一提
Jay Pritchett, by the way.
知道 我们见过很多次了
Yes, we've met many times.
记得吗 几年前 我借给你打车钱
Remember, a couple years ago, I loaned you money for a cab?
对啊
Oh, yeah, right.
妈妈
Ay, Mama.
她不是为了我们的钱
She's not after our money.
我怎么知道
How do I know?
她有钱 很有钱
She has money! Lots of it.
我要娶这个女人
And I'm marrying this woman.
我们下周婚礼见
I'll see you for the wedding next week.
下周
Ay, next week?
真快啊
That's very quick.
我不想给桑娅改变想法的机会
I don't want to give Sonia a chance to change her mind.
我肯定你不想
I'm sure you don't.
你不能娶桑娅
You can't marry my sister.
为什么
Why?
英文两字
Two words.
带连字符也可以算一个字
Maybe one, with a hyphen.
傍大款
Gold digger.
我很讨厌看到人
I've always hated to see people
以这种方式占别人便宜
take advantage of others in that way.
我不能让这种事发生在我家
I can't let that happen here.
但桑娅不是很有钱吗
But doesn't your sister have a lot of money?
如果她没钱 你会那么快就和她结婚吗
Would you be that quick to marry her if she didn't?
你有看到涅斯托尔吗
Hey, have you seen Nestor?
我把他送走了
I sent him off.
今天没人会拿别人的钱了
Nobody's taking anyone's money today.
我不需要他给我很多钱
Oh, I didn't need that much from him.
我只需要重新拍摄我的电影结尾
I just need to reshoot the end of my thesis film.
特效很差 布拉格一看就是假的
The special effects are weak, and Prague was clearly faked.
你到底在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?
涅斯托尔 他家很有钱
Nestor. His family's loaded.
我查了他的资料
I looked him up.
他是贝瑞勒兹家族的吗
He's a Berellez?
他们手里有一支足球队 十二家酒店
They own a soccer team, 12 hotels,
还有五个法官
and five judges!
真的吗
Oh, really?
我不在乎你是否想买一万个壁橱
Well, I don't care if you want to buy 10,000 closets.
我没上班
I'm not at work.
我想和我的孩子... 们共处
I am trying to bond with my child...ren.
拜拜
Bye.
你好
Hi.
实在抱歉 只是
So sorry about that. It's just -- Ugh.
总是有人要给我推销产品
People are constantly trying to sell me,
但真的不是所有时刻都合适谈生意 你懂吗
and it is not always appropriate, you know?
完全理解
I hear that.
妈妈们 妈妈们
Mommies, mommies.
盖理
Gary.
让我们从臀部拉伸开始
Let's start with a deep hip stretch.
我觉得这门课够难了 你怎么还能带双胞胎上
I find this class hard enough. How do you do it with twins?
在难也没有处理工作上
Well, uh, it's nothing compared to the babies
那些巨婴还难啊
I got to juggle at the office, huh?
我明白那种感觉
I know that feeling.
上下运动 更深一些
Now up and down, a little deeper.
有个欢迎婴儿的小吃店
You know, there's a baby-friendly tapas place
阿迪克斯和我一会去 你们愿意可以一起来
Atticus and I go to after, if you ladies are up for it.
我觉得现在不是交朋友的时刻 盖里
I don't think it's time to bond, Gary,
而且我挺确定你是告了这里才让你进来的
and I'm pretty sure you had to sue to get in here.
他有 向上
He did. And up.
我们不得不和解 向下
We had to settle. And down.
你们做什么样的衣橱
So, what kind of closets do you make?
因为我其实需要
Because I actually need --
我们下课再说可以吗
You know what? Would it be okay if we did this after class?
只是 我平常没时间和他们在一起
It's just, I get no time with them.
当然 当然
Of course, of course.
爬台阶怎么样了
Oh. Hey. How were the steps?
很好 很辛苦
Uh...so -- so great. So tough.
喜欢燃烧卡路里的感觉
Uh, love the burn.
帽子怎么回事 我都看不到你的眼睛了
What's up with the hat? I can barely see your eyes.
还是一样的眼眸
Uh, same old eyes.
我只是要去
I'm just gonna go ahead and, um --
为什么你的额头上有电影里排球的标志
Why is there a Wilson logo on your forehead?
我不知道 肯定是帽子上的
I don't know. Must be the hat.
没人会买账的
Nobody's buying it.
直接跳到告诉我们真相的部分吧
Just skip to the part where you tell us the truth.
行吧 我没爬楼梯
Fine. I-I never made it to the stairs, okay?
我分心了
I got distracted.
我是骗子 开心了吗
I'm a fraud. Happy?
我甚至都没去楼梯那儿
I never even made it to the stairs.
甚至都不知道在哪里
Don't even know where they are.
我不能说我
You know, I can't say I'm --
我对你一点都不失望 米奇尔
I'm not a tad bit disappointed in you, Mitchell.
只是独自踏上这段自我提升的旅程
It's just a little lonely going on this journey
我有点孤单
of self-improvement all by my--
-那是什么 -什么
- What is that? - Hmm? What?
你从博物馆哪里弄到这个的
What -- What part of the museum did you get this from?
很显然
Uh, well, apparen--
很显然 你不熟悉
obviously, you're not...
马蒂斯的羽毛时期
familiar with Matisse's feather...period.
你是不是在博物馆对面弄到的
Did you maybe get this across the street from the museum?
不是
Hmm? No.
如果是的话 你会有一个与众不同
'Cause if you had, you'd have a distinctive and sparkly...
闪闪发光手背印章
hand stamp!
我只需要一张票
I-I just need one ticket.
大家快点
Oh, my God, you guys, let's hurry!
快点去哪里
Hurrying where?
有个回顾展
Uh, there's a retrospective --
"七十年代的雪儿: 吉普赛人 流浪汉和小偷
"Cher in the '70s: Gypsies, Tramps and Thieves."
你丢下我自己去了
You went without me?
我们一直怎么说的
What do we always say?
每次看雪儿的经历都应该是
Every Cher experience should be
-共同的经历 -共同的经历
- a shared experience. - Shared experience.
我很抱歉 米奇尔
I'm -- I'm sorry, Mitchell.
如果我能让时光倒流
If I could turn back time --
敲敲
Knock knock!
把羽毛给我
Give -- Give me the feather.
不 把羽毛放在你的帽子里
No, put the feather in your cap.
只是来看看 博物馆怎么样
Hey, just checking in. How was the museum?
非常好 请坐
Oh, so great. Sit down!
小卡本来正想告诉我们
Cam was actually about to tell us
他对毕加索的了解
what he learned about Picasso.
我对他知之甚少
Oh, I know so little about him.
原来 他是出生在
Well, it -- it turns out he was born, um...
巡回表演的马车上
in the wagon of a -- of a traveling...show.
他的妈妈 真可怜
His mother, poor thing,
她被迫为大家跳舞
she was forced to dance for all --
你想让我教你打桥牌吗
You want me to teach you how to play bridge?
-当然 -我需要一个新玩伴
- Sure. - I need a new partner.
我和电脑玩总是赢
I keep beating the computer.
我们想邀请你们
Listen, we want to invite you guys
来参加今晚的晚餐聚会
to a dinner party tonight.
你们会很喜欢赞德和马特奥的
Yeah, you guys are gonna love Xander and Mateo.
他们刚在莫桑比克跑完超级马拉松
They just finished an ultramarathon in Mozambique,
他们也在那办讲座
where they're lecturing.
为了暖身开胃
And to build up an appetite,
我们玩短跑猜谜
we play sprinting charades.
还有一个搞笑版本的明星游戏
Yeah, and, uh, this silly version of Celebrity
只用狄更斯小说中的角色
using only characters from Dickens.
听起来真有趣
That sounds so fun.
我们失陪一下
We'll be-We'll be right back.
我们正在用大浅盘把芹菜摆成扇形
We were just fanning out some celery on a platter.
我想让他们走人
Okay, I want them gone.
哪怕你是指杀死他们 我也同意
Even if you mean kill them, I'm in.
我们该怎么办
I mean, what are we supposed to do?
像胡娇脸颊填充物掉下来后那样
Spend the next six months with our drapes closed,
羞得整整六个月都不拉开窗帘吗
like Pepper after one of his cheek implants fell?
他那歪脸还真是毕加索画风
Speaking of Picasso.
我们怎么才能脱身
How are we supposed to get out of this?
搬到西边去
Move out west.
那些小镇就是为了人间蒸发用的
That's what those towns are for -- disappearin'.
咱家离海边就一千六百米 哪来的小镇
We live a mile from the ocean. What town?
我脑子有病吗
What's wrong with me?
我太蠢了
I am so stupid!
亲爱的 怎么了
Sweetie, what is it?
她赢了我 这还是她第一次玩
She beat me, and she never even played before!
我真是个废物
I'm such a loser!
她还好吗
Is she okay, or...?
薇拉总是这样
Vera has this thing
不能每件事都做到完美她就抓狂
where she needs to be perfect all the time.
我们搬到这个社区的唯一原因
You know, the only reason we moved to this neighborhood
就是住在这里
was so we could be closer
离她被录取的精英学校更近
to this accelerated school she got into.
或许我们该重新考虑这个决定
Maybe we need to reconsider the move?
当然 我们还是会付这六个月的钱
Naturally, we'll pay for all six months.
好的
Yes.
我们该去和她聊聊
We should go talk to her.
抱歉 大伙
I'm sorry, guys.
我本来很期待一起吃芹菜的
I was looking forward to that celery.
我今天就想吃那些高热量的
I could really use a cheat day.
薇拉
Vera?!
莉莉 你怎么
Lily, how --
我把镜子放在那就能看到她的牌了
I set up my mirror so I could see her cards.
我别无选择
I had to!
她总让我感到低人一等 我受不了了
I couldn't stand her making me feel bad about myself.
不 我理解
No, no, I get it.
感觉他们好像也不介意让别人感到低人一等
I'm not sure they don't enjoy making people feel inferior.
你们俩就永远不会让人感到低人一等
Which is something you guys could never do.
等等 她是不是说
Wait, did she just say
我们永远不会让人感到低人一等
that we could never make people feel inferior
因为我们自己也不是什么人上人
because we're so inferior ourselves?
但用夸奖的语气说出来 让人不易察觉
But cleverly wrapped in a compliment to avoid detection?
也就是说 完美的基佬损人方式
In other words, the perfect gay zinger?
她或许不能高中毕业
Well, she may not finish high school,
但她在任何托尼奖派对都不会吃亏
but she will hold her own at any Tony party
-这辈子都不会 -没错 不会吃亏
- the rest of her life. - Yeah, she will. Yeah.
听你这么说我很遗憾
I'm really sorry to hear that,
但说实话 要是你妻子离开你
but honestly, if your wife left you
只是因为你错过了她生日
just because you missed her birthday --
是为了开车送你去机场
To drive you to the airport.
我听到了 曼尼 谢谢
I heard him, Manny. Thank you.
或许没有她你会过得更好
you're probably better off without her.
你说得对
You're right.
我只希望今晚去参加儿子的婚礼
I only wish I had something nicer to wear
能有件好衣服穿
to our son's wedding tonight.
要知道 咱俩的尺寸差不多
You know, you and I are about the same size.
不如我把燕尾服借给你
Why don't you borrow my tux?
真的吗
Really?
你一定要穿
I insist.
并且我还想另外给你样东西
In fact, I want to give you something else.
你的飞机
Your plane?
不 我只是在拿钱包
Uh, no, I was reaching for my wallet.
为了还欠着你的出租车钱
You know, to give you that money I s-still owe you for the cab.
自从那次在房顶
I've admired this plane
帮你拿飞机时摔下来 我就一直很喜欢它
ever since I fell off the roof getting it for you.
我好感动 好荣幸
I'm so touched and honored.
其实
Well, actually --
他从房顶摔下来了
He fell off the roof.
好吧
Fine.
尽情玩
Enjoy.
我要叫它萝伯塔
I will name her Roberta.
那飞机是带把的
It's a boy plane.
我好像把粘扣粘错了
I feel like I got the buckles wrong.
你觉得我穿这紧身衣看起来正常吗
Does this straitjacket look right on me?
越来越合你了[精神病人也穿]
More and more.
爸 我爱你
Dad, I love you,
但我没时间再陪你练其他魔术了
but I don't have time for another magic trick.
我找不到我的证件了
I can't find my ID,
申请太空总署的工作需要复印件
and I need a copy of it for this NASA job,
我的申请表必须在五点前寄出去
and my application has to be mailed by 5:00.
真抱歉 要我帮你找吗
I'm sorry. Can I help you look?
太让人绝望了
This is hopeless.
除非有办法能在邮局和车管局
Unless there is some way to jump the line
不用乖乖排长队
at both the post office and the DMV,
而这个时间能顺利开车到这两个地方
and the only way to get to either of them at this hour
只有走拼车专用道
is to drive in the carpool lane.
我们回来了
We're ba-a-ck!
我的天 我好想你们
Oh, my God! I missed you so much!
交给我 你看起来好累
Oh, I got this. You look so tired.
可我睡了一天了
But I've been napping all day.
不客气
You're welcome.
至少让我闻闻他们的头吧
Can I at least smell their heads?!
涅斯托尔
Nestor?
又是我 歌洛莉亚·普里契特
Hi. It's Gloria Pritchett again.
拜托你给我回电话
Please call me back.
我需要解释
I need to explain.
这都是一个大误会
This was all a big mistake.
涅斯托尔 你去哪了 我的爱人
Nestor, where are you, my love?
不
Ay, no.
桑娅
Sonia...
我有个坏消息要告诉你
I have very bad news to tell you.
让我先叫涅斯托尔过来 他是我的精神支柱
Let me get Nestor. He's my rock.
涅斯托尔
Nestor!
我那个独立的妹妹哪去了
Ay, what happened to my independent sister
我是那么崇拜她 因为她不需要男人
that I admired so much because she needed no man?
他在哪里
Where...is he?
我以为他是来傍大款的
Well, I thought he was a gold digger,
所以我把他赶走了
so I chased him out.
你说你干了什么
You did what?!
塞翁失马焉知非福 好歹你的钱还在啊
But the silver lining is that you still have all your money!
什么钱 我有个屁钱啊
What money? I don't have any money!
你这话什么意思
What do you mean?
辣酱生意红火 你不是赚了很多钱吗
The money from the hot-sauce business that you're doing so well.
没有 那全是谎言
No, it was all a lie.
我编来让他不会怀疑我别有居心
I just didn't want him to be suspicious.
看 我戴的是铝制耳环
Look, I'm wearing aluminum earrings!
我的耳朵都要戴发绿了
They're turning my ears green!
我用足足两年才钓上这个有钱帅气的傻逼
It took me two years to land that rich, beautiful moron.
我还能去哪里找到这样的大款啊
Where am I going to get that kind of money?!
哎哟 我被绊倒了
Oh, I tripped!
快来个人帮我找律师
Someone call a lawyer!
你才没被绊倒
You didn't trip.
有的 就是有 你看
Yes, I did! Look!
地上都是湿的
Uh, the floor is all wet.
桑娅 这招在豪华游轮上不好使
Sonia, that didn't work at the Princess Cruise ship,
在我这也不会有用
and it's not going to work here.
每次我想好好过日子
Every time I try to get my life together,
你就总是要搞破坏
you always ruin it for me.
你欠我一个有钱老公
You owe me a rich husband.
我再给你找一个就是了
I'll find you one.
这里多得是又老又有钱的男人
There are plenty of old, rich men around here
你想怎么玩就怎么玩
that would do anything that you say.
某些老男人还有听力呢
Some of them can still hear.
这位是谁啊
Oh. Who's this?
他是...
He's, um...
全城搞树篱[对冲基金]最牛逼的人
He's the best hedge guy in town.
快恭喜他吧 他刚入手一架飞机
Congratulate him. He just got a new plane.
搞对冲的啊
Ohh. A hedge guy.
真有意思
Fascinating.
那你是怎么进入这行的呢
And how did you get started in that business?
我买了剪子[快艇队]
I bought the clippers.
你穿得这么帅是要去哪里吗
And where are you going, dressed so nice?
去参加婚礼
A wedding.
我好喜欢婚礼啊
Ohh, I love weddings.
能有幸请你陪我一同参加吗
Would you like to accompany me?
乐意之至
I would love to!
能坐[带]你的飞机去吗
And can we take your plane?
当然啊 没问题
Yeah, sure.
为什么我们家的园丁穿着你的燕尾服
Why is our gardener wearing your tuxedo?
为什么涅斯托尔不在了
Why is Nestor gone?
让我先去把门锁上
Let me lock the door first.
歌洛莉亚 你又毁我人生
Gloria! You ruined my life again!
这是你的戒指吗
Is this your ring?
是的
It is!
这是你的袜子吗
Is this your sock?
是的
It is.
这是... 你的牌吗
Is this...your card?
我忘了
I don't remember!
现在所有东西都物归原处
Now everything is where it belongs.
除了这根蜡烛 它应该是被放在...
Except for this candle, which obviously belongs...
钢琴上
...on the piano!
-天啊 -什么
- Oh, my God! - What?!
是的 感觉我就是来丢人的
You're right. It's like I want to fail!
老爸 你别瞎说 你的表演超赞啊
Dad, stop being crazy. Your act is great!
结尾平淡就表示这是个无聊的表演
It's a flat finish, which means it's a flat act.
很明显是有两根蜡烛啊
It's obviously two candles.
我是趁你们分心的时候把第二支放过去的
I put the second one over there while I was distracting you
就是把牌射进这蠢葡萄那会儿
by throwing a card into that stupid grape.
我们到家啦
We're home!
我的宝贝们
My babies!
感觉一天没见到你们了呢
I feel like I haven't seen you all day!
你们今天玩得开心吗
Did you have fun today?
想知道也很简单
Well, that's easy to find out.
让我上传一下今天的婴儿镜头影片
Let me just upload this baby cam footage.
你 你说什么
The what -- what was that? Hmm?
他们身上其中一颗纽扣是摄像头
Oh, one of their buttons is actually a camera.
虽然画质不怎么样 不过...
It's not the greatest quality, but...
等等 你带我的孩子们去酒水铺了吗
Wait, you took my babies to a liquor store?!
没有 那是...
No, it's the --
是酒品博物馆啦
it's the wine museum.
卢克 明明是王牌酒水铺
It's Ace Liquor, Luke.
老娘可是打从15...
I've been going there since I was 15...
满21岁后15分钟首次踏入那里
minutes past my 21st birthday.
我真是不敢想象....
Well, I am horrified --
等等 等等 我刚刚快进了
Wait, wait, wait, I just fast-forwarded,
看到你跟一个女人在瑜伽班上说话
and it's you talking to some lady at a yoga class.
她是杂志上的人
She's from the magazine!
你为了生意出卖我宝宝的色相吗
You pimped out my babies for a sales pitch?
有谁受到伤害吗
Who did it hurt?
茵素
Poppy!
太无耻了 我个人无法忍受...
Oh, disgusting. Personally, I can't stand --
车管局的某个保安
Some guard at the DMV
让我们五个月大的婴儿咬了一口他的热狗
giving our five-month-old a bite of his hot dog.
他只是帮忙照看了一下下而已啦
He only watched them for a second.
我本来还很高兴你们今天都愿意帮忙带孩子
I was so happy you all wanted time with the babies today,
因为最近我有种感觉
because lately, it has felt like
你们好像都不想跟孩子们沾上边
you didn't even want to be bothered with them.
结果原来你们都是无利不起早
Turns out you only want to help when it can help you.
我心里都有一点纳闷我们为什么还要住这里
Part of me wonders why we even stay here.
因为你在这里不用交房租加饭钱吗
Because you eat and live here for free?
我说了只有"一点"
I said "part."
好啦 我不是要说他们做的对
Okay, I'm not saying what they did was great,
但家人不就是这样吗
but isn't that what families do?
互相帮助彼此
Help each other out?
如果能够帮助到家人
And are we ever really too young
难道有年纪太小一说吗
to come to our family's aid?
你开什么玩笑 竟然打算说服我们
You're not seriously trying to get us
借孩子给你拿去表演魔术
to let you use them for your magic trick, are you?
真的是我的牌
It is my card!
感谢各位热烈的支持
You guys have been great.
不过是时候帮我可爱的小助手
But I should be getting my beautiful assistant here
脱下燕尾服 换上温暖舒适的睡衣了
out of this tuxedo and into some warm jammies.
太客气啦
You guys.
表演成功都是你们的功劳
It's you that make it work.
我对之前的事感到很抱歉 希望我没有太无礼
So, I'm sorry about earlier. I hope I wasn't rude.
没事 我完全理解 你现在有空一起吃东西吗
Please. I totally get it. Are you free for a bite now?
当然 我想我还是有点时间的
Sure. I guess I got a couple minutes.
完美
Perfect!
我去"直达塔帕斯"餐厅订个位子
I'll get us a table at Straight to the Tapas.
好极了 到时候见
Great. Meet you there.
我只是想摆脱他 我们不去
I'm just getting rid of him. We're not going.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
他的衬衫之前提上去的时候
When his shirt rose up earlier,
我看到一个爱探险的朵拉的纹身
I saw a Dora the Explorer tattoo.
我可不想听到这背后的故事
And I do not want to hear the story behind that one.
你知我知 不可外传
This stays between us.